All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece
must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World,
Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island,
which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman pirates, led by Horty Jones
and assisted by Vander Decken,
plot to overthrow King Neptune.
Friends or enemies, huh?
Don't ask me.
Cause I'd say, it's up to you!
The Big Clash!
The Straw Hats versus 100,000 Enemies!
Uh, hey guys, is that him?
I really hope not,
cause he's invaded the Navy headquarters twice,
and we're no Navy!
Well, that looks like his pirate ship.
Not to mention his crew, so yeah.
the années in Physics.
Ha ha ha!
Ha, come on really?
What kind of weirdo hides inside a shark?
I'm more concerned with how that skeleton and the others managed to escape from the Ryugu Palace.
About time you showed up, Straw Hat!
I can't believe he came!
Madam Shirley! That pirate you were talking about!
He's here!
Yeah, he just saved the princess and the king!
The Straw Hat Boy.
Yeah, yeah, I'm here. How was that?
It could have gone worse, considering it was Luffy.
Hmm. Not exactly what we had planned, but I can't argue with the results.
No! You're staying right here!
Don't fight. It's pointless.
Come on. We're just wasting time.
Yes, right. If we don't hurry, they'll kill father.
I already told you, Jinbei! Get out of my way so I can go and kick this horny guy's ass!
And I told you to wait! You aren't listening at all!
Let me finish speaking!
Now, how would you describe the relationship between us?
We're friends.
That's right.
Although it is a simple matter for us, our two peoples have been struggling to establish such a relationship for decades now.
I left you a message saying not to fight Horty, because I didn't want you facing him recklessly.
Don't you see?
Horty, think of how the fishmen will view you.
If you rush in and show aggression towards Horty, you'll be viewed as nothing more than just another human bully oppressing our kind.
That is not what we want.
No! You should be a hero!
One that saves the island!
A hero? Hell no!
Why why?
Obviously because we're pirates!
Come on! Heroes are great!
But I'm not one!
Seriously!
Do you even know what you're asking me to do?
Let's say there's a chunk of meat, right?
Pirates will have a banquet and dig right in.
But a hero would give it to other people instead of eating it!
Screw that! My meat is mine!
What a reason.
It figures, dummy.
Luffy! I'll let you have all the meat you want! Just do as I say!
That's fair.
No way!
I'll make this simple.
There will come a time when I need your help so you'll rush in when that moment arrives.
Okay.
Good.
But first, the plan.
We'll get caught, on purpose, to get us close.
Afterwards, while their attention's on me, then one of you pirates will sneak out of Megalo's stomach and get yourself into position to make your attack.
Did you say a stomach?
The Celestial Dragon's letter. They have it. We need it.
Hold on. What's this letter?
Jinbei, remember? Luffy was sleeping through most of your story. He doesn't know.
In short, the letter is something Queen Otohime acquired ten years ago at great personal risk. It will define the very future of this island.
They'll also have the key we'll need to release the king from his bonds.
One of your crewmates must retrieve them.
Which one of you's up to the task?
I'm pretty good at stealing, but still, I think I'll need Robin's help.
Of course.
Good. Once you've managed to free the king, get out. I'll call Luffy and we'll take over.
After you emerge from Megalo's body, the people of Fishman Island will understand your intent.
Because they'll see you and I working together against the common foe.
Princess, I must ask that you stay somewhere safe outside the plaza. It's for the best.
We'll pass the letter to you, whereupon the entire royal family can't escape.
During this time, the rest of you will have to head to Ryugu Palace to rescue your imprisoned friends.
Once they're free, get to the plaza to back us up as soon as possible.
As for how you go about saving them, well, that's for you to deal with.
Come on! Be specific!
Wow! You can count on us big time!
After all, we've got the Sunny, right?
So no worries. We'll be there.
Once this is set in motion, there's no turning back. We must succeed!
You, everyone here, respects Jinbei.
Whether they're a civilian or outlaw, they'll follow after his example.
Mm-hmm. That's right. So if they see Jinbei working with a human, even a pirate, they'll cheer you on or maybe even fight beside you.
I mean, it's possible.
Straw hat?
Please, Luffy.
I'm only doing this because you asked me to. Got that? I mean it! Having people cheer for me? No thanks! I don't like it!
I'm more for taking their money and running away.
Speak for yourselves! I'd go to the depths of hell if I knew the mermaids would be there to cheer me on!
Very well, then.
Sounds like everything is settled, then.
All right. Let's do this thing!
Hmm. Wait.
Yeah? What's up? Something wrong?
What's our codename?
Are you kidding? Who cares?
Can we go already?
At any rate, it appears you were able to save your friends from the palace.
Straw hat!
Huh? Papa Goo!
What's up? It hasn't been that long.
I know, I know! But I almost died! Many times! Because of those guys!
Huh?
That's straw hat Luffy! He's human! And a pirate! But on our side!
He showed up right when Princess Shirohoshi called for him!
From the looks of things, he's here to help us Jinbei save the country from Hordi's men!
Shirohat!
Isn't it sweet how they cling to you?
But you've only delayed the king's inevitable demise!
After all, you are nothing but a human!
Your beauty outshines all others, princess!
Now that we've met, would you be willing to show me your panties?
You can't ask her that!
Then show me yours!
No way in hell!
Okay, we're back! About time!
They're all ignoring you!
That's just because I was using my inside voice!
Nami Swan!
Now that I've saved those idiots from the palace, you have to love me!
Right?
Whatever!
Wait, he did what? Liar? We got to the exit ourselves!
Maybe! However, you never would have escaped! Without me!
That's a joke! Right, you guys?
Wish I could say it was!
But he left out the part where Brooke was a ghost!
What'd you say?
You heard right!
Our escape was only possible because of my splendid new ability!
I need you to find the key! I mean, I need you to find the sword!
Please!
There's no time!
Stay away, ghost!
I'm a ghost!
All right, that's weird. How exactly does this ghost know my name?
Come now! We're friends!
Yo-ho-ho-ho!
Ah! No, we're not! I don't have any friends that are ghosts!
Wait, you're Boondaddy, aren't you?
Yo-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Oh no! It's here!
What are you doing, Brooke? Hurry!
Before it's too late!
I feel sorry for the wait!
Oh, no biggie!
Ow!
Here! Your sword!
Nice cut! Way to go!
Heck yeah! We're outta here!
Three-sword style!
Okay, that was way too much!
You think?
I'm running out of strength!
I gotta get a breath!
Damn!
I'm gonna die!
Ow!
What the heck?
Hey! I came to get ya!
Great, they're still alive!
It was very exciting!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
It sounds like your new ability is still alive!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
I'm running out of strength!
Oh, I'm running out of strength!
I-I gotta get a breath!
Damn!
I'm gonna die!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
What the heck?!
Hey! I came to get ya!
Great, they're still alive!
It was very exciting!
It sounds like your new ability is pretty amazing, Brooke!
I'm sure it'll come in handy!
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
It sounds like your new ability is pretty amazing, Brooke!
I'm sure it'll come in handy!
come in handy. Anyway, Luffy knocked their captain out in one hit. Why don't they seem
more worried about that? You're right. That's odd.
Shira Hoshi, it's your mom's letter. Here you go.
I can't tell you how much this means to me. I know it may look like an ordinary piece
of paper, but it's this island's hope.
That's enough. Weepy Hoshi, it's not safe.
He's right. You weren't meant to be caught, so you must leave. Now, while you can.
Wait, Luffy. What, did you call me?
Huh? Just now, it was almost my name, but...
Yeah, I was wrong about you. You're a wuss, but more than just a crybaby.
So I'll call you Weepy Hoshi. It's an upgrade.
When a person feels as if they've been wronged, well, then it's only natural that they would
turn to hate. That man.
Hordy. He's doing exactly that.
But you chose not to hate. A coward wouldn't do that. Hardship has only made you stronger
in the end.
Nami is right. You endured. Princess, I'm proud of you.
I appreciate the thought. But still, I feel like I caused everyone trouble by keeping
this secret to myself.
I'm sorry. You're mistaken. You've done quite well.
Your intentions were pure. Just like those who have come before you.
You can't tell them you have to hold it in.
Listen. Don't become angry on my behalf. I don't want that.
Our heroes planted a seed in your heart, and it has blossomed beautifully. You have lived
by their example well. If everyone else thought the way you do, then there would be no more
fighting, and the conflict between fishmen and humans would be over at last. You may have
suffered through those past years alone, but that doesn't make that time meaningless.
Single-handedly, you are a defender, protecting the virtues of others day after day.
But today, we're here. We'll protect them for you.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You're still a crybaby. That's for sure.
Strahat! Take him down!
I should have known Vander Decken was going to fail me. He couldn't even get rid of one
lousy princess.
Captain Horty!
It's as I thought. The energy steroid is still coursing through his veins.
Given how much he took, I'd be surprised if it wasn't!
He's back up! They're done for!
Her power is too great. It really is the stuff of legends. Once I found out it was real, I knew I had to eliminate her as soon as possible.
Sir. But then, you got in my way. Admittedly, I should have known something was wrong when you were captured without putting up a fight, Jinbei.
You really like these humans, don't you? People like you were the worst. You've completely forgotten your pride.
See? You grew up with Tiger in our district. And let's not forget Arlong. He was like your brother. Both of them were beaten or killed by humans.
But instead of avenging them, you wouldn't get in bed with the humans. It's pathetic. Jinbei, godless like Neptune. But soon, everything is going to change.
Once I'm king, that is. Hear that? I'll start with the world summit. That'll be the perfect place.
With every ruler in the surface world in one place, they'll be easy to kill. Then the whole world will learn to fear our underwater kingdom.
Their kingdoms in disarray will drag the humans into the depths and enslave every last one. In time, there won't be a soul left to stand against us. And we will rule the great pirate era.
Oh, yes. You pirates. Wheel-pow. The same as everybody else. Just you wait. You see? These humans are more than capable of holding their own, yet they kneel before me.
That's right. In a moment, you'll be just like them. Straw hats. I'll be king of the fishmen, king of the humans, and king of the pirates.
Is that so?
And to think there are only ten of you here to stand in my way. What can you possibly do when we're 100,000?
How are they supposed to fight all of them? Boss Jinbei's side is too outnumbered. I don't like these odds. Are they going to be okay?
They're the only hope we have left. So if they lose, Horty takes everything. They must win. Because if they don't, that march is going to take our homes away.
Fight! Boss Jinbei! You got this, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat!
Kill them! New fishmen pirates!
Here they come! No way we can fight this many at once! We're done for!
This is exactly the reason I don't like hanging out with you guys!
Before this begins, it's been a pleasure traveling with all of you.
Don't say that! Gah!
There are so many enemies. Wow. If I try to count them all, my eyes may pop out. Then again, I don't have eyes. So they can't!
Just 100,000? That's nothing we can't handle, right?
Hey, wait! You're just saying that because you're hiding behind us!
And here I go! It's time to shine! Super armored me! All right!
Let's do this already! Get over here!
In case you can't count, we're each going to have to take down 10,000 of these guys to win this fight.
They have numbers, but it doesn't make them stronger. I mean, it's not like they're Navy Admirals or anything. So don't crap yourself.
After these guys, you're next! Number 10,001! Bring it on! I can't wait!
Hey, Luffy!
Oh, no!
Luffy?
Those 4 million berries are mine!
No, they're mine! It's too easy!
Kill him!
Son of a bash!
skill 3
ah! What the hell just happened!
Ah! What the hell just happened!
And now we're in person, he's got an eye to nose!
But he didn't do anything, and he still knocked them all out!
Hey! Get up, guys! Come on!
Damn! He took down half of us in an instant!
That was 50,000 of our men! What did he even do?
Did everyone see that?
Yeah, but I don't know what it was!
So much power.
For one so young.
Wait! Did the Straw Hat guy really do that?
Yeah! Too cool!
That hockey...
That training paid off, I see.
Unreal. I mean, Conqueror's hockey? Scary.
Sure is, but I'd expect no less. Otherwise, he couldn't be my captain.
Oh my! Wilfite!
Your name's Hordy, right? I'm about to kick your ass.
You want to become the king of a country or whatever?
Fine, I don't care.
But king of the pirates?
Nuh-uh. That's my job.
Despite Luffy's display of hockey, the sheer number of Hordy's forces proves overwhelming.
As the new Fishman pirates close in on Shirahoshi, Zoro and Sanji launch an assault.
With the last two years still fresh in their minds, the Straw Hat's training is put to the test,
as they unleash a flurry of fearsome new techniques.
On the next, One Piece!
Deadly attacks one after another!
Zoro and Sanji join the battle!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Deadly attacks two after another!